http://www.ecoshell.com/privacy

Eco-Shell, LP
(“Eco-Shell”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) recognizes the importance of privacy. In this Privacy Policy, we describe how we collect, use, and disclose information that we obtain about visitors to our website www.ecoshell.com (the “Site”) and users of the services available through our Site (the Site, and the services available through it, are hereinafter collectively referred to as the “Services”).
By using any of our Services, you agree that your information, including personal information, will be collected, used, and disclosed as described in this Privacy Policy. Your use of our Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes.
Information We Collect
How We Use Information
How We Disclose Information
Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms
Third-Party Services
Do Not Track Disclosure
Interest-Based Advertising
Third-Party Collection
Security
Your Choices
Children
Contact Us
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Information We Collect
We collect information about you directly from you and automatically about you through your use of our Services. We may combine information we collect through various sources.
Information We Collect Directly from Users. We may collect information about you directly from you. For example, if you contact us through our Site, we will collect your name, email address, and/or phone number. We will also collect any other information that you provide to us through our Services.
Information We Collect Automatically. We automatically collect information about you through your use of our Services, including, without limitation: Internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, domain name, the website that led you to our Services, the website to which you go after leaving our Services, the dates and times you access our Services, and device identification information. Please see our Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms section below for more information.
How We Use Information
We use the information that we collect, including personal information, for the following purposes:
Providing and Improving Our Services. To provide and maintain our Services and products; to improve our Services and products; to develop new features, products, or services; to perform technical operations; and for other service and support purposes.
Research and Analytics. To analyze how you interact with our Services; to monitor and analyze usage and activity trends; and for other research, analytical, and statistical purposes.
Marketing and Communications. To communicate with you about your account and use of our Services; to send you product, service, or event updates; to respond to your inquiries; to provide you with news and newsletters, special offers, promotions, and other information we think may interest you; and for other informational, marketing, or promotional purposes. Our communications with you may include communications via email. Please see our section regarding Your Choices for more information about how to change your communications preferences.
Protecting Rights and Interests. To protect the safety, rights, property, or security of Eco-Shell, the Services, any third party, or the general public; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to prevent or stop activity which Eco-Shell, in its sole discretion, may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity; to use as evidence in litigation; and to enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use.
Legal Compliance. To comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding; to respond to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process; or as part of an investigation or request from law enforcement or a governmental authority.
How We Disclose Information
We disclose the information that we collect, including personal information, as described to you at the time of collection, as consented to by you before disclosure, and/or as follows:
Affiliates. We may disclose information to current or future affiliates or subsidiaries for research, marketing, and other purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Service Providers. We may disclose information to our vendors, service providers, agents, or others who perform functions on our behalf.
Business Transfers. We may disclose information to another entity in connection with, including during negotiations of, an acquisition or merger, sale or transfer of a business unit or assets, bankruptcy proceeding, or as part of any other similar business transfer.
Protecting Rights and Interests. We may disclose information to protect the safety, rights, property, or security of Eco-Shell, the Services, any third party, or the general public; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to prevent or stop activity which Eco-Shell, in its sole discretion, may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity; to use as evidence in litigation; and to enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use.
Legal Compliance. We may disclose information to comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding; in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process; or as part of an investigation or request from law enforcement or a government official.
Aggregate and De-Identified Information. We may disclose aggregate, anonymous, or de-identified information for marketing, advertising, research, compliance, or other purposes.
Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms
We and our service providers use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track information about how you use our Services. We or our service providers may combine this information with other information, including personal information, we collect about you.
Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to a computer’s hard drive through a web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Services, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track your activities while using our Services. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers provides information about how to prevent a computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify upon receiving a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. If you disable cookies, you may be able to browse certain areas of the Services, but some features may not function (e.g., you may not be able to stay logged into your account).
Clear GIFs, pixel tags, and other technologies. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs (also referred to as web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags), in connection with our Services to, among other things, track your activities, help us manage content, and compile statistics about usage of our Services. We and our service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML emails to you, to help us track email response rates, identify when our emails are viewed, and track whether our emails are forwarded.
Third-Party Services
We may use third-parties, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate use of our Services. We or our service providers use these tools to help us understand use of, and to improve, our Services, performance, and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies, such as web beacons or local storage objects (LSOs), to perform their services. To learn more about Google’s privacy practices, please review the Google Privacy Policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/. You can also download the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on to prevent data from being used by Google Analytics at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Do Not Track Disclosure
Our Services do not respond to Do Not Track signals. For more information about Do Not Track signals, please click here. You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in the Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms section above (e.g., by disabling cookies).
Interest-Based Advertising
We or our service providers may use third parties such as network advertisers to display advertisements on our Services, to assist us in displaying advertisements on third-party services, and to evaluate the success of our advertising campaigns. You may opt out of many third-party ad networks, including those operated by members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). For more information regarding this practice by NAI members and DAA members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including how to opt out of third-party ad networks operated by NAI and DAA members, please visit their respective websites: www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp (NAI) and www.aboutads.info/choices (DAA).
Opting out of one or more NAI member or DAA member networks only means that those members no longer will deliver targeted content or ads to you. It does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content or ads on our Services or other services. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextual advertising) or from entities that are not members of the NAI or DAA. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit an opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your NAI or DAA opt out may no longer be effective.
Third-Party Collection
Our Services may contain links to third-party websites and applications provided by third parties. Any access to and use of such linked websites, applications, or third-party services is not governed by this Privacy Policy but instead is governed by the privacy statements of those third parties. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third parties, and we encourage you to read their privacy statements.
Security
We have taken steps to help protect the personal information we collect. However, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security. You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your device or account by, among other things, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess and keeping your log-in and password private. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.
Your Choices
Correcting or Deleting Personal Information. You may correct or request deletion of your personal information by updating your profile or emailing us at sales@ecoshell.com. Please note that we may retain certain information about you as required by law or as permitted by law for legitimate business purposes (e.g., in accordance with our record retention policies or to enforce our Terms of Use).
Opting out of Email Communications. We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you. You may opt out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the email or emailing us at sales@ecoshell.com. Please note that it may take up to ten business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt out of receiving marketing emails from us, we may still send you non-promotional emails (e.g., about your account with us).
Children
Our Services are not targeted to children under thirteen years of age, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under thirteen. If we discover that a child under thirteen has provided us with personal information, we will promptly delete such personal information from our systems.
Contact Us
If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our Services or for further information about our data privacy policies and practices, please contact us at sales@ecoshell.com.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes, including any material changes, to this Privacy Policy on our Site.
Eco-Shell, LP
5230 Grange Road | Corning, CA 96021
Phone: 1-(530)-824-8794 | FAX: 1-(530)-824-8798
©2017 Eco-Shell, LP - All Rights Reserved.
Legal & Privacy | Terms & Conditions
